UsefulDesk — a WhatsApp-first CRM for gym businesses.
I'm on the Settings page. I'll connect a WhatsApp Business Account.
I click "Connect WhatsApp" to start Embedded Signup.
[public_profile] Facebook Login for Business opens.
I select my business portfolio.
[business_management] The app reads the business assets I share.
I create a new WhatsApp Business Account.
Using WhatsApp display only, so it provisions a test phone number.
[whatsapp_business_management] The app registers the number and subscribes the WABA for webhooks.
I complete the steps and the popup closes.
Back on the CRM: "Meta connected" — WhatsApp API successfully connected.
I verify with the built-in test API button. It returns success.
The credentials and phone number are live.
[whatsapp_business_messaging] I open WhatsApp on a real phone and send a message.
The message appears in my CRM's shared inbox.
I reply directly from the CRM inbox.
The reply is delivered and shows in the WhatsApp conversation on the phone.
A business connects its WhatsApp account via Embedded Signup.
Our platform then sends and receives messages on their behalf.
In production, gym owners connect their number to send renewal reminders and payment follow-ups.